ebookxyz.com 2010-08-23

# Privacy Policy | Ebooks share | Free Download Ebooks | Ebook download | Audio Books | Magazines

**

ebookxyz.com – Privacy Policy

**

****  
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by ** **ebookxyz.com****. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Currently, ** **ebookxyz.com**** may provide aggregate statistics about our traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personal identifying information.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

**Modification of Privacy Policy**

****ebookxyz.com**** reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter or update the Privacy Policy and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates.

**Diclaimer  
None of the files shown here are hosted or transmitted by this server. The links are provided solely by this site's users. The administrator of this site (ebookxyz.com) cannot be held responsible for what its users post, or any other actions of its users. You may not use this site to distribute or download any material when you do not have the legal rights to do so. It is your own responsibility to adhere to these terms. If you have any doubts about legality of content or you have another suspicions, feel free to contact us at forextradingxyz@gmail.com **
